kevkeka.com 2016-03-14

# Telugu Movie News | Telugu Movie Reviews | Andhra News & Political Updates - kevkeka.com

**Privacy Policy:**

www.kevkeka.com welcomes our viewers into the site. We value your privacy and here by declare on what is the information we collect and what we do with it.

**Information Collection**

You can visit/surf our website www.kevkeka.com without providing any personal information. However, if you choose to avail of certain services on our website, you shall be required to provide certain information for the registration and/or access to such services/web pages. Such information may include, without limitation, your name, email address, contact address, mobile/telephone number(s), sex, age, occupation, interests, financial information, content, IP address, standard web log information and such other information as may be required for your interaction with the services.

**Usage of Information**

Some of the feautres on www.kevkeka.com might need to provide or submit your information. This information provided by you shall not be sold/given/rented to third parties (third parties for this purpose do not include our group / holding / subsidiary companies and or our service partners / associates) for marketing purposes and other related activities without your prior consent. We use all this data in better service of our customers. 

**Out Bound Links**

This website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by the website or to our other related websites provided it appears at the footer of the page therein. It does not apply to third party advertisements which appear on our websites and we suggest you read the privacy statements of such advertisers.

**Third Party Ads**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

**Cookies**

We use a software technology called "cookies" for several purposes, depending on the type of cookie employed. Within kevkeka.com, we use what are commonly called "session" cookies, meaning that they only last as long as you are online. We use these cookies to identify you as a valid subscriber so that we can deliver music to you, to ensure that no one else can sign on simultaneously with your account from another computer and to help us personalize your service experience based on your registration preferences (such as genre). We may also use session cookies to help us facilitate any promotions or surveys that we provide. As part of the sign-in process, we may also use what are commonly called "persistent" cookies which stay with you after your session is over and you are offline. We only use these cookies in connection with a sign-in feature that allows you to save your member name and password so that the next time you sign in, these fields will be pre populated for you. This cookie is only offered in conjunction with certain Affiliate Sites that choose to make it available and it can only be activated if you select that option during your sign-in. If you select this option you can always deselect it each time you sign-in.

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and such other places we deem appropriate so that you are updated about the manner we collect information, what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
